<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> 

<FAQList>

  <FAQ Question="What skills should I enter in Saba Cloud?"
         Answer="&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Only enter skills that you are currently using or are skilled to perform.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do not enter older historical skills that you used to use but that are no longer used or you are no longer proficient in.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be sure to follow the compliance rules to complete this activity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="What steps do I have to take to update my profile?"
         Answer="&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Confirm if you are in an exempt role by checking the Role Guide. If still unsure, check with your manager &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Access the training assets on the Skills Management myDXC page:&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Read the Read Me First document&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Read the Saba Cloud - Compliance Criteria document&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Read the Employee Job Aid and Employee Guide for completing your profile&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Confirm with your manager is there are Business specific guidelines for your organization to follow&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Only enter skills you that you are currently using and skills that you are proficient in and can perform now. They should not enter any historical skills that they no longer use or use or are no longer proficient in or active in the market place&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ensure your entries are compliant&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Follow the How to add a Resume document - Instructions to enter your resume&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Notify your manager when your entries are complete so they can begin their review&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="Where do I find all the training assets for the Skill Profile updating?"
       Answer="&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;All training assets are located on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.dxc.com/our-company/global-functions/integrated-workforce-management/analytics-and-intelligence/dxc-skills-management.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;myDXC Skills Management&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;myDXC Skills Management&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be sure to read the ReadMe First document for descriptions of each asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="I need to delete some skills; how do I do that?"
       Answer="&emsp;Please refer to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.dxc.com/content/dam/private/our_company/global_functions/integrated_workforce_management/skillsmanagement/SkillDeletionGuide.pdf
&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skill Deletion Guide&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="How do I register for a course?"
       Answer="1.	Click on the waffle and select the ME tile. The My Plan page opens
2.	On the My Plan page, click the Actions button and select Add Learning
3.	An Assign Learning window will open. Choose Register and then click Next
4.	Using the search and filter functionality locate the course you wish to enroll in. If there are more than one class click the Select class link . A list of class IDs will open. For ILT/VILTs you can mouse over a class to see the dates/times of the class. 
5.	After locating a class in the list click the Action > Arrow  to move the class into your selected learning.
6.	Click Register
7.	A registration confirmation window opens indicating that you have been successfully registered for the selected course. Close the window to return to you My Plan page.
8.	If the course is Web-based, locate the course in your plan and click the Launch button to start the training. 
">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="How do I cancel my registration for a course?"
      Answer="If you have enrolled for any learning you either no longer wish to complete (e.g. WBT) or cannot attend (ILT/VILT) the learning still appears on your My Plan page in DXCU.  To unregister/drop learning from your training plan, follow these steps: 

1.	Click on the waffle and select the ME tile. The My Plan page opens with a list of learning you are enrolled in.
2.	Find the learning you wish to drop and from the Actions column click the drop-down and select Drop. A cancel order window opens. 
3.	Click Yes and wait for the cancel order window to close automatically.
4.	The learning should no longer appear in your plan. 

NOTE: Any learning that has been assigned to you, either by a system rule or a manger/person, cannot be removed. You would have to contact the manager/person who assigned it and have them un-assign it.  You may also submit an HRConnect support case for assistance.
">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="How do I save a copy of my certificate of completion?"
      Answer="In the Action column click the drop down list next to the completed learning and select Export Certificate. A PDF version of the certificate will be available at the bottom of your screen for you to save, or open/view.
">
  </FAQ>
    <FAQ Question="How can I evaluate the training I have taken?"
      Answer="Click on the waffle and select the ME tile. My Plan page opens. Click Completed Learning from the left navigation. Next to the course you want to evaluate, there will be Actions. Click to expand and select Evaluate Training.
">
  </FAQ>
    <FAQ Question="How do I add a training taken outside of DXC University to my completed learning?"
      Answer="To add any training (course, seminar, webcast, third party certifications, etc.) to your completed learning, which is not listed in DXC University or you took externally, follow these steps:
1.	Click on the waffle and select the ME tile. The My Plan page opens
2.	On the My Plan page, click the Actions button and select Add Completed Course
3.	In the Add Completed Course window, click the Add New button
4.	Enter required information:
a.	Course name
b.	Completed Date (the date on which you want to mark the course as completed)
5.	Enter optional information:
a.	Description
b.	Class End Date (the date on which you finished the course)
c.	Score
6.	Click Additional Details to enter other optional information:
a.	Registration Date
b.	Delivery Type
c.	Location
d.	Duration
e.	Skills
f.	Attachments
1.	Click Submit for Approval button
2.	Close the message box that opens &quot;The completed course entry is saved successfully.&quot;
3.	Inform your manager to review the entry you have made for the external training and approve it – Manager will have to login into DXC University, Click on their Message Center envelope, review the entry, and approve it. 
Once it is approved you can refer the following steps to verify the course completion being tracked:
1.     Click on the waffle and select the ME tile. The My Plan page opens
2.     Click Completed Learning. The course name will be now be added to your Completed Learning with a description &quot;The course has been completed externally&quot;, indicating that it is an ad hoc entry.
3.     You may have to click the Filters button, use the filters available to you, and then click Apply Filters to locate the training. 

">
  </FAQ>
</FAQList>
