<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> 

<FAQList>

  <FAQ Question="What skills should I enter in Saba Cloud?"
         Answer="•	Only enter skills that you are currently using or are skill in to perform in.&lt;br /&gt; 
•	Do not enter older historical skills that you used to use but that are no longer used or you are no longer proficient in.&lt;br /&gt;
•	Be sure to follow the compliance rules to complete this activity">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="What steps do I have to take to update my profile?"
         Answer="All non-exempt employees are expected to do the following:&lt;br /&gt;
•	Confirm if you are in an exempt role by checking the Role Guide. If still unsure, check with your manager&lt;br /&gt;
•	Access the training assets on the Skills Management myDXC page:&lt;br /&gt;
•	Read the Read Me First document&lt;br /&gt;
•	Read the Saba Cloud - Compliance Criteria document&lt;br /&gt;
•	Read the Employee Job Aid and Employee Guide for completing your profile&lt;br /&gt;
•	Confirm with your manager is there are Business specific guidelines for your organization to follow&lt;br /&gt;
•	Only enter skills you that you are currently using and skills that you are proficient in and can perform now. They should not enter any historical skills that they no longer use or use or are no longer proficient in or active in the market place&lt;br /&gt;
•	Ensure your entries are compliant&lt;br /&gt;
•	Follow the How to add a Resume document - Instructions to enter your resume&lt;br /&gt;
•	Notify your manager when your entries are complete so they can begin their review
">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="Where do I find all the training assets for the Skill Profile updating?"
       Answer="•	All training assets are located on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.dxc.com/our-company/global-functions/integrated-workforce-management/analytics-and-intelligence/dxc-skills-management.html&quot; title=&quot;myDXC Skills Management&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;myDXC Skills Management Page&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
•	Be sure to read the ReadMe First document for descriptions of each asset.
">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="I need to delete some skills; how do I do that?"
       Answer="Please refer to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.dxc.com/content/dam/private/our_company/global_functions/integrated_workforce_management/skillsmanagement/SkillDeletionGuide.pdf
&quot;&gt;Skill Deletion Guide&lt;/a&gt; at
https://my.dxc.com/content/dam/private/our_company/global_functions/integrated_workforce_management/skillsmanagement/SkillDeletionGuide.pdf
">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="My question is not listed above. Where do I find more information?"
       Answer="Please contact your DXC Legal Attorney or Contracts Negotiator. DXC Legal professionals are assigned by business unit, function and geographic location. Please direct your &lt;a href=&quot; https://techdirect.corp.int.hpe.com/support/submitNew.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;technical questions here&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="My question is not listed above. Where do I find more information?"
      Answer="Please contact your DXC Legal Attorney or Contracts Negotiator. DXC Legal professionals are assigned by business unit, function and geographic location. Please direct your &lt;a href=&quot; https://techdirect.corp.int.hpe.com/support/submitNew.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;technical questions here&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.">
  </FAQ>
  <FAQ Question="My question is not listed above. Where do I find more information?"
      Answer="Please contact your DXC Legal Attorney or Contracts Negotiator. DXC Legal professionals are assigned by business unit, function and geographic location. Please direct your &lt;a href=&quot; https://techdirect.corp.int.hpe.com/support/submitNew.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;technical questions here&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.">
  </FAQ>

</FAQList>
